[
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "0",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "1",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "2",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "3",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "4",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "5",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "6",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "7",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "8",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "9",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "10",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "11",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "12",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "13",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "14",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "15",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "16",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "17",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "18",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0\n\ninput: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "19",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0",
            "Three 0 ; Four 5 ; Five 0",
            "Five 0 ; Four 5 ; Three 0",
            "Five 0 ; Three 2 ; Four 0",
            "Seven 0 ; Three 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Four 6 ; Six 0",
            "Four 0 ; Four 6 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Seven 5 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 5 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Seven 6 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Seven 6 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Three 0 ; Three 1 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Three 1 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "0",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "1",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "2",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "3",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "4",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "5",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "6",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Nine 0 ; Five 3 ; Zero 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Nine 0 ; Five 3 ; Zero 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "7",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "8",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eight 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Eight 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "9",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "10",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eight 0 ; Six 7 ; Zero 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Eight 0 ; Six 7 ; Zero 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "11",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "12",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "13",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Six 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Six 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "14",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Eight 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Eight 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "15",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "16",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "17",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "18",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0\noutput: Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,3,3,3,3,3,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "19",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 1 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 1 ; Three 0",
            "Four 0 ; Six 7 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Six 7 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Four 0 ; Three 2 ; Seven 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Eight 7 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 7 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Four 0 ; Five 3 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Five 3 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "0",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "1",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "2",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "3",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "4",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "5",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Five 0 ; Five 8 ; Five 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Five 0 ; Five 8 ; Five 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "6",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "7",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "8",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "9",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "10",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "11",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "12",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "13",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "14",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0",
            "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "15",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "16",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "17",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Nine 5 ; Five 0",
            "Three 0 ; Nine 5 ; Three 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Seven 0 ; Eight 8 ; Five 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Seven 0 ; Eight 8 ; Five 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "18",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "Six 0 ; Five 1 ; Four 0",
            "Eight 0 ; Five 1 ; Two 0",
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Three 0 ; Eight 8 ; Four 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0\n\ninput: One 0 ; Eight 8 ; Six 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Six 0 ; Eight 8 ; Minus Five 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Six 0 ; Eight 8 ; Minus Five 0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input: 0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: 0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput: ",
        "task_name": "19",
        "s2l_tools": [
            "One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0",
            "Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0",
            "Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0",
            "Two 0 ; Five 8 ; Eight 0",
            "Four 0 ; Five 8 ; Six 0",
            "One 0 ; Three 2 ; Eleven 0",
            "Three 0 ; Three 2 ; Nine 0",
            "One 0 ; Five 8 ; Nine 0",
            "Three 0 ; Five 8 ; Seven 0",
            "Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0"
        ],
        "s2l_label_tools": "Eight 0 ; Four 6 ; Three 0",
        "s2l_prompt": "input: One 0 ; Ten 4 ; Four 0\noutput: Three 0 ; Ten 4 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Two 0 ; Nine 2 ; Four 0\noutput: Four 0 ; Nine 2 ; Two 0\n\ninput: Six 0 ; Four 6 ; Five 0\noutput: ",
        "response": "Eleven 0 ; Four 6 ; Zero 0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "Eleven 0 ; Four 6 ; Zero 0"
    }
]